[Music]
hi guys
third here I'm from FWD and the
privilege of being one of the
participants floors or Jason's practical
enterpreneur and the puck just hits you
right where it matters
no nonsense ideas everything that was
shared were applicable items for
aspiring interpret news what I like the
most about the top is it brings you back
there or it brings you back to your
values brings you back to asking
yourself why you want to do the things
that you want when I get to read the
full good most modern day on insights
which is I'm appreciating I mean with
with a limited time we had a very good
experience this they will the speaker is
Angela Hoffa so thank you I mean Jason
and you for giving your time starts I'd
like to thank sir Jason are really good
for keep inspiring future create the
interpreter sir Jason LSE
[Music]